<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Celeste Basken</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Celeste Basken</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Celeste Basken 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>International Association of Landscape Ecology</title>
      <link>/blog/ialeconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ialeconference/</guid>
      <description>I gave a Poster Presentation at the International Associate of Landscape Ecology, North America, conference in April 2021.
Orders of Magnitude: Changes in Area Burned Per Year in the NE United States Dropped from Millions to Thousands of Acres Per Year</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise Movement Press Conference</title>
      <link>/blog/sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sunrise/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with the youth-led Sunrise Movement for two years. Recently, the team that I led within my local hub of the movement convinced our County Council and County Executive to endorse the Federal Green New Deal and call on the Biden Administration and Congress to take a strong stance on climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crew Mid-Atlantic Erg Sprints 2nd Place</title>
      <link>/blog/crewergsprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/crewergsprints/</guid>
      <description>I placed second in the 500m sprint in the lightweight category at the Mid-Atlantic Erg Sprints 2020.
This winter season crew competition involves rowing on an ergometer stationary rowing machine. Read more about my experience on Blair High School crew here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model United Nations Award</title>
      <link>/blog/mun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/mun/</guid>
      <description>I was awarded Best Delegate at the Garfield Model United Nations Conference in Fall of 2019.
Read more about my involvement with Model UN here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Presents Double-Edged Sword in Addressing Opioid Addiction</title>
      <link>/blog/curioussciencewriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/curioussciencewriters/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2019 I had the unique opportunity through the Curious Science Writers program to follow a biomedical research study at the National Institutes of Health, interview a scientist behind the study, and then write a journalism article for teenagers about the importance of the research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
