<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Celeste Basken</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Celeste Basken</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Celeste Basken 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>International Association of Landscape Ecology</title>
      <link>/blog/ialeconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ialeconference/</guid>
      <description>I presented original research at the International Associate of Landscape Ecology, North America, conference in April 2021.
My poster presentation was the culmination of a yearlong virtual internship with The Nature Conservancy, where I learned the programming language R and software GIS in order to create data visualizations of data about historic fire amounts in North America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Collaboration; Coming of Age in a Pandemic</title>
      <link>/blog/film-collaboration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/film-collaboration/</guid>
      <description>As the head of SilverLens, my school&amp;rsquo;s documentary film program, I fascilitated a collaboration with other high schools in the area to combine our content about teenage life during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise Movement Press Conference</title>
      <link>/blog/sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sunrise/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with the youth-led Sunrise Movement for two years and am now a hub coordinator. In spring 2021, the team that I led within my local hub of the movement convinced our County Council and County Executive to endorse the Federal Green New Deal and call on the Biden Administration and Congress to take a strong stance on climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crew Awards</title>
      <link>/blog/crewergsprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/crewergsprints/</guid>
      <description>My boat, the women&amp;rsquo;s 8+, won first place at the Capitol Sprints race in the summer of 2021. My boat also won third in the women&amp;rsquo;s 4x at the Philadelphia Youth Regatta the same summer, both for Washington Rowing School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model United Nations Award</title>
      <link>/blog/mun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/mun/</guid>
      <description>I was awarded Best Delegate at the Garfield Model United Nations Conference in Fall of 2019.
Read more about my involvement with Model UN here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Presents Double-Edged Sword in Addressing Opioid Addiction</title>
      <link>/blog/curioussciencewriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/curioussciencewriters/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2019 I had the unique opportunity through the Curious Science Writers program to follow a biomedical research study at the National Institutes of Health, interview a scientist behind the study, and then write a journalism article for teenagers about the importance of the research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
